[
   {
      "question": "who is current president of India?", 
      "answer": "Ramnath Kovind",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Which planet in our solar system is known as the Red Planet?",
      "answer": "Mars",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Who was the first woman Prime Minister of India?",
      "answer": "Indira Gandhi",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Who was the first woman President of India?",
      "answer": "Pratibha Patil",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Which place never gets the vertical rays of the Sun?",
      "answer": "Srinagar.",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Which countries are separated by the Radcliffe Line?",
      "answer": "India and Pakistan",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Which state is called the ‘sugar bowl’ of India?",
      "answer": "Uttar Pradesh",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "What is Gir National Park in Gujrat famous for?",
      "answer": "Lion",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Which is the highest peak in India?",
      "answer": "Mount Everest",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Which is the largest state of India?",
      "answer": "Rajasthan.",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "When did Virat Kohli become India's Test captain? ",
      "answer": "2014",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Which among the following is the smallest bird in the world?",
      "answer": "Hummingbird",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Who is ceo of google?",
      "answer": "Sundar Pichai",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "The Indian Constitution recognizes total ………… Languages.",
      "answer": "22",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Which is the first city attacked by atom bomb?",
      "answer": "Hiroshima",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "1st World War started in",
      "answer": "1914",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Russian Revolution ending the Tsarist autocracy in the year",
      "answer": "1917",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "USSR (Union of Soviet Socialist Republics) came into existence in the year",
      "answer": "1922",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Beginning of the Great Depression begin in the year",
      "answer": "1929",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "2nd World War started in",
      "answer": "1939",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Dropping of Atom Bombs on Hiroshima and Nagasaki in the year",
      "answer": "1945",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Launch of Sputnik 1, marking the beginning of space age in the year",
      "answer": "1957",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Landing of Apollo 11 with Neil Armstrong on the surface of moon in the year",
      "answer": "1969",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "Chernobyl disaster happened in the year",
      "answer": "1986",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "World Wide Web invented, Reunification of Germany in the year",
      "answer": "1990",
      "score": 20
   },
   {
      "question": "Dissolution of USSR in the year",
      "answer": "1991",
      "score": 30
   },
   {
      "question": "End of apartheid in South Africa happened in which year",
      "answer": "1994",
      "score": 10
   },
   {
      "question": "9/11 attack on World Trade Center in the year",
      "answer": "2001",
      "score": 20
   },
   {
      "question": "Tsunami in Indian Ocean in the year",
      "answer": "2004",
      "score": 30
   }
]